tootoomart.com 2010-06-26

# Security & Privacy -- tootoomart.com

### Privacy Policy

Welcome to tootoomart.com, a B2B online trading platform leading in China. We respect your privacy and want to protect your personal information. To learn more, please read our Privacy Notice. This declaration will specify our policy regarding the protection of your privacy. If you have visited our website, that will be considered to be your acceptance to this privacy policy.This Privacy Notice applies only to this Site. This privacy policy does not necessarily apply to our offline collection of your personal information. Please see below for details.

#### How can we protect your privacy?

The security of your personal information is very important to us. We never sell or rent your personal information to any third parties under any circumstances. We value your trust very highly, and will work to protect the security and privacy of any personal information you provide to us and will only use it as we have described in our Privacy Policy. 

#### Safe purchase at tootoomart

We want you to feel completely secure when ordering from tootoomart. We use a technology called Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), which encrypts (or encodes) sensitive information before it is sent over the Internet. 

#### Our Privacy Policy

#### A.What personal information do we collect?

As set forth in more detail below, tootoomart ("tootoomart" or "We") collects personal information that you provide when using the tootoomart web site ("Site"). This information includes your first and last name, email address and a password when you create your tootoomart account. You can browse this Site without creating an account, but you will need to create an account when you purchase something and in order to take advantage of certain features, such as "Save for Later," "Address Book" and the other tootoomart services. We may ask you to confirm your personal information when you contact our Customer Service department. This will allow us to protect your confidentiality by verifying your identity. 

tootoomart does not intentionally collect personal information about children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 18 but at least 13 years of age you may use this Site only under the supervision of a parent or legal guardian who agrees to be bound by the tootoomart Terms of Use. Children under the age of 13 may not use this Site and parents or legal guardians may not agree to the tootoomart Terms of Use on their behalf. If you do not agree to (or cannot comply with) any of the tootoomart Terms of Use, do not use this Site. 

**a) Purchase Information**

When you make a purchase from tootoomart, we collect your name and payment method information. We collect this information in order to bill you for your purchase. We also collect information that allows us to ship your order. This includes the name, address, and phone number of the intended recipient(s). When you create an account at tootoomart, you can choose to save your billing information in "My tootoomart." You can also save one or more shipping addresses in your tootoomart Address Book. You may change or delete this saved information anytime. Simply go to My tootoomart. Log in with your ID and password, then edit or delete whatever personal information you wish.

**b) Services account information**

We collect personal information from users who wish to use any of the Tootoomart services, including but not limited to, Tootoomart's Transaction Platform. In order to use these services you must provide your email address and password or create an account at Tootoomart. We also collect certain technical information from your computer each time you request a page during a visit to Tootoomart. This information may include your Internet Protocol (IP) address, your computer's operating system, browser type and the address of a referring web site, if any. We collect this information to enhance the quality of your experience during your visit to this Site and will not sell or rent this information to any third parties. We also contract with third parties to provide us with data collection and reporting services regarding our customers' activities on this Site and to track and measure performance of our marketing efforts. These third parties may use cookies and may receive anonymous information about your browsing and buying activity on this Site. None of your personally identifiable information (such as your name, address, email address, etc.) will be received by or shared with these third parties.

**c) Contacting Tootoomart**

We will use your email address to respond to your questions, suggestions, and/or requests for assistance in using this Site. 

**d) Other personal information we may collect**

From time to time, Tootoomart may conduct surveys and contests via this site, email, other media. If you choose to participate, we may request your name, email address, mailing address and other personal information. We will never sell or rent such information to any third parties.

#### B. How we use your personal information?

Information we collect on Tootoomart may be used for billing purposes, to fulfill your orders, to communicate with you about your order and our site, and for internal marketing purposes. If we encounter a problem when processing your order, we may use the personal information you provide us with to contact you.

What’s more, By creating an account at tootooomart.com you will be able to shop faster, be up to date on an orders status, and keep track of the orders you have previously made.

**e) When and with whom can we share your personal information?**

We never sell or rent your personal information to any third parties under any circumstances. We will share personal customer information only with our agents, representatives, service providers, and contractors for limited purposes, including fulfilling customer orders; offering certain products and services in connection with this Site; communicating to customers; providing customer service; storing, sharing and retrieving customers' photo images; enhancing and improving clients' purchase experience; enabling access to our partners' web sites; providing a personalized purchase experience; preventing fraud and completing payment method processing. Aside from the purposes described above, we will never share your personal information with any other third parties unless we have your express permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the disclosure is required to prevent harm or injury (such as product recalls, fraud, claims or other liability) or to comply with valid legal processes (subpoenas, warrants) or as required by law. We may share aggregated demographic and statistical information with our partners. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

**f) How can you control the use of your personal information?**

You can modify or delete your personal information anytime, simply go to Mytootoomart, log in with your ID and password, then edit or delete whatever personal information you wish. We recommend that you do not divulge your Password to anyone. Our personnel will never ask you for your Password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited e-mail. If you share a computer with others, you should not choose to save your log-in information (e.g., User ID and Password) on the computer. Remember to sign out of your Account and close your browser window when you have finished your session.

**g) How can we protect the security of your personal information?**

Your personal information is protected by the password you created when you created an account at Tootoomart (or another password you chose after changing a previous password). Please keep this password confidential. No Customer Service Associate or any other representative of Tootoomart will ever ask you for your password. The confidentiality of your password is yours to protect. You may change it anytime by going to Mytootoomart. Log in with your email address and password, then click "Change Name, Email & Password" and enter a new password. We realize that making purchases at Tootoomart, or any other web site, requires trust on your part. We value your trust very highly, and pledge to you, our clients, that we will work to protect the security and privacy of any personal information you provide to us and that your personal information will only be used as set forth in this Policy. 

#### C. Updates this policy

If we change or update this Privacy Notice, we will post changes and updates on this Site so that you will always be aware of what information we collect, use, and disclose. We encourage you to review this Privacy Notice from time to time so you will know if the Privacy Notice has been changed or updated.
